Preliminary Inventory to the Carla A. Hills Papers, 1964-1993
Hoover Institution Archives
Carla Anderson Hills Papers
1964-1993
77007
Hoover Institution Archives
141 cubic foot boxes, 219 manuscript boxes, 1 oversize box (268 linear feet)
Correspondence, reports, memoranda, speeches, and printed matter, relating to civil litigation involving the United States government, especially lawsuits involving President Richard M. Nixon; housing and community planning and development in the United States during the presidential administration of Gerald R. Ford; activities of the Republican Party, American Bar Association, and Alliance to Save Energy; and American foreign trade policy during the presidential administration of George Bush.
Hills, Carla A., 1934-
Access
Collection is open for research. Collection stored off site; a minimum of two days notice is required for use. Boxes may be requested through Stanford's online catalog at http://searchworks.stanford.edu
The Hoover Institution Archives only allows access to copies of audiovisual items. To listen to sound recordings or to view videos or films during your visit, please contact the Archives at least two working days before your arrival. We will then advise you of the accessibility of the material you wish to see or hear. Please note that not all audiovisual material is immediately accessible.
Acquisition Information
Materials were acquired by the Hoover Institution Archives in 1977, with additional increments thereafter.
Accruals
Materials may have been added to the collection since this finding aid was prepared. To determine if this has occurred, find the collection in Stanford University's online catalog at http://searchworks.stanford.edu/. Materials have been added to the collection if the number of boxes listed in the catalog is larger than the number of boxes listed in this finding aid.
Related Collection(s)
Carla Hills papers, Special Collections, Stanford University
Biographical/Historical note
American lawyer and government official; assistant attorney general, Civil Division, 1974-1975; secretary of housing and urban development, 1975-1977; trade representative, 1989-1993.
Scope and Contents note
Correspondence, reports, memoranda, speeches, and printed matter, relating to civil litigation involving the United States government, especially lawsuits involving President Richard M. Nixon; housing and community planning and development in the United States during the presidential administration of Gerald R. Ford; activities of the Republican Party, American Bar Association, and Alliance to Save Energy; and American foreign trade policy during the presidential administration of George Bush.
Alliance to Save Energy.; American Bar Association.; Nixon, Richard M. (Richard Milhous), 1913-1994.; Republican Party (U.S.: 1854- ); United States. Dept. of Housing and Urban Development.; United States. Dept. of Justice.; United States. Office of the U.S. Trade Representative.; City planning--United States.; Community development--United States.; Conservatism.; Energy policy--United States.; Government litigation--United States.; Housing--United States.; Law--United States.; Lawyers--United States.; Statesmen--United States.; United States--Commerce.; United States--Foreign relations.; United States--Politics and government--1974-1977.; United States--Politics and government--1989-1993.; United States--Politics and government.
- A-95 REVIEW PROCESS (Box 1)
- ABRAMS, Milton A.
- ACCEPTING INVITATIONS FROM MEMBERS OF CONGRESS TO PARTICIPATE IN THEIR RADIO/TV PROGRAMS
- ADMINISTRATION (Cody)
- ADMINISTRATION/MANAGEMENT FUNCTIONS REORGANIZATION TASK FORCE
- ADMINISTRATION WEEKLY REPORT
- ADMINISTRATIVE CONFERENCE OF THE UNITED STATES - HUD PARTICIPATION
- ADMINISTRATIVE DECENTRALIZATION AS A COMPLEMENT TO REVENUE SHARING: A Case Study of HUD Programs
- ADMINISTRATIVE OPERATIONS FUND
  - Administrative Practice/Procedure Senate Subcommittee Hearings S.2715 to Amend Administrative Procedure Act
- ADMINISTRATIVE SANCTIONS
- ADP SYSTEMS PLANNING/POLICY COMMITTEE
- ADVANCE MORTGAGE CORPORATION (Robert Mylod, President)
- ADVERSE ACTIONS FY-75 ANNUAL REPORT
- ADVISORY COMMISSION ON HOUSING AND URBAN GROWTH
- ADVISORY COMMISSION ON INTERGOVERNMENTAL RELATIONS
- ADVISORY COMMISSION ON INTERGOVERNMENTAL RELATIONS, Briefing Materials, May 20-21, 1976 -
- AFFIRMATIVE MARKETING AGREEMENTS
- AGING
  - House Select Committee on Aging -, 9/25/75
  - Senate Special Committee on Aging -, 10/8/75
- AIRLIE HOUSE
- ALASKA - Meeting w/Senator Ted Stevens, 7/22/76
- ALASKAN TASK FORCE
- ALASKAN NATURAL GAS TRANSPORTATION ACT OF, P.L. 94-586, 1976
- AMERICAN FEDERATION OF GOVERNMENT EMPLOYEES, LOCAL 476, Washington, D.C.
- AMERICAN NATIONAL RED CROSS, BOARD OF GOVERNORS
- ANNUAL CONTRIBUTIONS LEGISLATION
- ANNUAL HOUSING SURVEY
- ANNUAL PERFORMANCE RATING
- ANNUAL REPORT (HUD) 1974 (Box 2)
- FY-76 ANNUAL TRAINING NEEDS SURVEY
- APPROPRIATIONS COMMITTEE DIRECTIVES RE 1976 HUD INDEPENDENT AGENCIES APPROPRIATIONS BILL
- APPROPRIATIONS BILL FY 77 - House/Senate Conference Agreement H.R. 14233
- HOUSING APPROPRIATIONS COMMITTEE
  - 1977 Housing Appropriations Committee Hearings
  - House Appropriations Committee, (1976)
- SENATE APPROPRIATIONS COMMITTEE
  - Subjects for Appropriations Hearings
  - Senate Appropriations Committee
- AREA WIDE ALLOCATION
- AREAWIDE HOUSING OPPORTUNITY PLANS
- ARLINGTON HEIGHTS LITIGATION
- ASIAN-AMERICAN PROGRAM OFFICE
- AS-IS SALES (JULIAN LEVI)
- ASSOCIATED GENERAL CONTRACTORS OF AMERICA
- AUDIT GUIDE
- AUDIT REPORTS
  - Operational Surveys
  - Audit Plan - FY 76
- AUTHORIZATION LEGISLATION (Box 3)
  - House Authorization Bill - H.R. 11769
    Scope and Contents note
    (now known as H.R. 12945)
  - Senate Authorization Bill - S.3159
    (now known as S.3295)
  - Senate Authorization Bill (S.3295) - Conference Report
- BACK PAY
- BALTIMORE LOW RENT CONVENTIONAL PUBLIC HOUSING REHAB
- BARRIERS (Elderly/Handicapped)
- BART (San Francisco Bay Area Rapid Transit System)
- BASSETT, M. GRACE
- BATTERY PARK PROJECT
- BICENTENNIAL
  - Background Material
  - Bicentennial
- BLACK STUDENT FUND
- BLACKMORE, ANDREW
- BLAIR, DENNIS C.
- HUD BOARD OF DIRECTORS CALENDARS
- BOCK, MARGUERITE S.
- BOIS D'ARC PATRIORS, et al. v. CITY OF DALLAS, et al., CA USDC, Northern District of Texas, Dallas Div., CA #3-75-0906D
- BOSTON HOUSING AUTHORITY
- BROOKINGS ECONOMIC POLICY FELLOWSHIP PROGRAM
- BROWN, JOHNNIE D.
- BUDGET ACT OF, 1974 (Box 4)
- BUDGET (Kliman)
- BUDGET BRIEFING (Remarks) 1/15-16/77
- BUDGET FY-76 OUTLAYS
- BUDGET
  - Budget FY-77 Recommendation on Appeal through Volume #1, November, 19
  - Budget FY-77
  - Administrative Expenses Appropriations and Accounts for FY-77
  - FY-77 Objectives/Operating Plans and FY-78 Budget - Budget Procedures and Schedule
- BUDGET - FY 77 (Section 8)
- BUDGET FY-77 RECOMMENDATIONS ON APPEAL, - Volume II, December 75 through September, 1976
- FY-77 AUTHORIZATION/APPROPRIATION TASK FORCE
- FY-78 CDBG AUTHORIZATION
- BUDGET FY-78- Volume #2 -, October, 1976 through December, 1976
- BUDGET Appeal, 1978
- BUILDING EMERGENCY CONSERVATIONS STANDARDS BILL, H.R. 8650, Housing Committee, Banking, Currency/Housing
- BUILDING/CONSTRUCTION TRADES DEPARTMENT (General)
- BUSINESS-GOVERNMENT RELATIONS COUNCIL
- BUSING
- CABINET MEETINGS
- CABINET MEETINGS -- -- STATE OF THE STATES (Governors), 12/18/75
- CAMP DAVID --, 6/17-18/76
- CAREER EDUCATION PROGRAM -- FY-77
- CARL, BERNARD J.
- CARPETING
- CARTER, JIMMY (Box 5)
- CASH vs. DEBENTURES PROJECT MORTGAGE INSURANCE CLAIMS
- CENSUS OF HOUSING
- CITIES -- FISCAL PROBLEMS
- CITIZEN CORRESPONDENCE
- CITIZEN HOUSING/PLANNING COUNCIL OF NEW YORK, INC., MEETING, 2/9/76
- CITIZEN PARTICIPATION
- CITY OF BOSTON v. HILLS, et al., USDC, D. Mass. CA #75-902-C
- CITY OF CHEYENNE, WYOMING v. U.S., et al., USDC, Wyoming, Civil #74-182/C-75-17 (Consolidated)
- CIVIL EMERGENCY PREPAREDNESS
- CIVIL RIGHTS ACT OF, 1968
- CIVIL RIGHTS TASK FORCE ON INSURANCE COMPANY REDLINING
- CIVIL SERVICE CASES
- CIVIL SERVICE RETIREMENT LAW
- CIVIL SERVICE COMMISSION EXECUTIVE PERSONNEL SYSTEM
- CLAIMS COLLECTION
- CLEARANCE SECTION, 8 FORMS
- CLIFTON TERRACE APARTMENTS PROJECT NO. 000-55034
- CLOTHING FOR KIDS
- COALITION FOR BLOCK GRANT COMPLIANCE, DETROIT, MICHIGAN Administrative Complaint
- CO-INSURANCE PROGRAM
- COLLECTIVE BARGAINING
- COLLEGE HOUSING (GENERAL)
- COLLEGE PARK URBAN RENEWAL AUTHORITY
- COLTON, KENT W.
- COMBINED FEDERAL CAMPAIGN
- COMMENDATION LETTERS (HUD)
- COMMERCIAL BANK TRUST DEPARTMENTS -- SENIOR INVESTMENT OFFICERS LUNCHEON
- COMMISSION ON EXECUTIVE, LEGISLATIVE/JUDICAIL SALARIES, REPORT, DATED DECEMBER, 1976
- COMMISSION ON FEDERAL PAPERWORK
- COMMITTEE FOR ECONOMIC DEVELOPMENT
- COMMITTEE, NATIONAL COMMISSION ON PRODUCTIVITY AND WORK QUALITY
- COMMITTEE ON GOVERNMENT PATENT POLICY OF THE FEDERAL COUNCIL FOR SCIENCE AND TECHNOLOGY
- COMMUNITY DEVELOPMENT PROGRAM GRANT FIRST ANNUAL REPORT TO CONGRESS, 12/30/75
- COMMUNITY DEVELOPMENT PROGRAM GRANT SECOND ANNUAL REPORT TO CONGRESS, 12/30/76
  - Community Development Program Grant First Annual Report to Congress -- Press Release/Fact Sheet, 1/8/76
  - Community Development Program Grant First Annual Report to Congress -- Miscellaneous Brief/Correspondence
  - Brookings Study of Community Development Block Grant Allocations
- COMMUNITY DEVELOPMENT BLOCK GRANT PROGRAM, Volume #7, October 1976 through January 1977
- COMMUNITY DEVELOPMENT BLOCK GRANT PROGRAM -- House Housing Subcommit Hearings, 11/18/75
- COMMUNITY DEVELOPMENT BLOCK GRANT - Administrative Complaints
- COMMUNITY DEVELOPMENT GRANT PROGRAM
  (Section 8 Subsidized Rental Program)
- COMMUNITY DEVELOPMENT GRANT PROGRAM "A Provisional Report"
- COMMUNITY DEVELOPMENT BLOCK GRANT RECONNAISANCE PAPER
- COMMUNITY DEVELOPMENT GRANTS FY-76 (Deficit)
- COMMUNITY DEVELOPMENT BLOCK GRANT - Legislative Evaluation
- Community Disposal Operations Fund (Box 6)
- Condominium Hearings - House Committee on Banking, Currency/Housing Subcommittee - General Oversight re Negotiation, 5/19/76
- Conference of Southern Black Mayors
- Confirmation Procedures
- Congress
- Congressional Budget Office Report "Sustaining a Balanced Expansion", 8/13/76
- Congressional Correspondence -- Volume #4, January 1976 - January 1977
- Congressional Investigations
- Congressional Testimony
- Consumer Guide (HUD)
- HUD Plan for Consumer Representation - Volume #2 -, November 1975
- CARF Organization
- HUD Plan for Consumer Representation
  - HUD Plan for Consumer Representation - Vol. #1 thru, October 1975
  - Consumer Involvement in HUD Decision Making
  - A Consumer Affairs Program for the Department of Housing and Urban Development
- Community Planning and Development (CPD) (Meeker)
- Complaint Correspondence
- Comprehensive Employment and Training Act (CETA)
- §701 Comprehensive Planning Assistance Program - Vol. #3, July 1976 thru January 1977
- §701 General
- §701/FEA Agreement for Coordination of Activities
- §701 Intra-Departmental Task Force
- §701 Interagency Demonstration with Middle Atlantic Governor's Coastal Resources Council (MAGCRC)
- Condominiums
- Task Force for Standardization of Condominium Requirements
- Condominium Consumer Protection Act of Hearings on S.2273, 1975
- Condominium and Cooperative Housing Report -----, 8/21/75
- Consumer Affairs
  - Consumer Affairs (Miscellaneous)
  - Book "Consumer Affairs Tarp's" (Study of Consumer Complaint Handling)
- Consumer Protection Act S.200
- Construction Industry Association of Sonoma County, etc., et. al. v. THE CITY OF PETALUMA, 9CA No. 74-2100 (Box 7)
- Contract Complaints
- Contracting at HUD
- Contract Retainage
- Contracting Task Force to Assign Desirability of Consolidating
- Cooperative Housing
- Cost Over Runs
- Cost Revenue Impact Analysis for Residential Developments: A HUD Research Project Report
- Council of Housing Producers
- Council of State Community Affairs Agencies
- Council on Wage/Price Stability
- Counseling
- Crawford, H.R.
- Crime Insurance Program
- "D"
- Data Systems
- Default Monitoring System Notebook
- Default Reports
- Deferred Mortgage Interest Re: Payment Act of, 1976
- Deferrals - 235 and 701
- Delegation of Authority
- Delinquency/Foreclosure Index
- Democratic Research Organization -- Committee to Investigate A Balanced Federal Budget, 4/29/76
- Department of Commerce
- Department of Defense
- Memorandum of Agreement Section 318 - Department of Defense
- Department of Health, Education and Welfare (General)
- Department of Health, Education and Welfare (Staff Meeting)
- Department of Health, Education and Welfare (Civil Rights)
- Department of Interior
- Department of Justice
- Department of Labor (General)
- Department of State
- Department of Transportation
- Department of Transportation Concorde Decision
- DOT/HUD Joint Report to Congress
- Department of Treasury
- Secretary Hills Housing Management Flow Charts (Box 8)
- Departmental Management Initiative (1975 Steering Committee)
- Departmental Handbook "Programs of HUD"
- Departmental Publications
- Departmental Training Plan
- Departure Plans -- Line Assistant Secretaries
- Deregulation
- Detroit Economic Club
- Detroit Trip, 4/14/76
  - MSHDA - Detroit Trip
  - Detroit Trip Press
- Detroit
  - Detroit -- Max Fisher
  - Detroit
- Detroit
  - Congressman Brodhead
  - Report to CAH for October by [UNK] Binford
  - Detroit -- Meeting with Mayor Young and Max Fisher 12 12/7
  - Detroit - Tripartite Agreement Meeting, 3/25/75
- DETROIT (Box 9)
  - Detroit/General/Miscellaneous
  - Detroit -- Congressional Correspondence
  - Detroit -- Current Detroit Problems
  - Detroit -- Testimony Requests
  - Detroit -- Demolition Contractor Suspension
  - Detroit -- Downtown Detroit Proposed Multifamily Apartment Project
  - Detroit -- Moving Detroit Forward
  - Detroit -- Allocation of Section 8 Contract Authority
- Detroit
- Direct Cash Assistance (DCA)
- Disaster Relief Act of, Public Law 93-288, 1974
- Dispersal by HUD/By Courts
- Distinguished Civilian Service Awards Board
- Domestic Council
- Duke Manor
- Economics
- Economic Policy Board
  - Economic Policy Board and Council on International Economic Policy Joint Meeting, 7/30/75
  - Economic Policy Board and Council on International Economic Policy Joint Meeting, 5/14/75
  - Economic Policy Board and Council on International Economic Policy Joint Meeting, 3/26/75
  - Economic Policy Board (General)
- Economists
  - Government Economists, Meeting with Secretary, 5/2/75
  - Outside Government Economists, Meeting with Secretary, 5/9/7
  - Government Economists, Meeting with Secretary, 8/20/75
  - Outside Government Economists, Meeting with Secretary, 9/5/7
  - Economists Luncheon, 6/22/76
- Elderly and Handicapped (Holt) (Box 10)
- Electric Power Demonstration
- Emergency Employment Appropriation Act, H.R. 4481
- Emergency Homeowners Relief Act
  - Title I - Foreclosure
    - (a) Handwritten notes/miscellaneous background
    - (b) Report to Congress
- Emergency Housing Act of (Correspondence), 1975
- Residential Tax Credit in H.R. 2166
  - HUD Tax Credit Proposal
  - Tax Credit Legislation, H.R. 2166
- Emergency Housing Legislation
  - Effects on Emergency Legislation Press
  - Emergency Housing Bill
  - Emergency Housing Legislation
  - Interest Groups Statements
  - Legislative History
  - Emergency Homeowners Relief Act S.1457 (AKA Mortgage Foreclosure Relief Act)
- Emergency Housing Legislation
  - Emergency Home Purchase Act of - Tandem, 1974
  - Housing Bill Veto
  - Housing Bill Veto (Press/Miscellaneous)
  - Reuss - H.R. 4485 Emergency Middle Income Housing Act
- Emergency Housing Legislation (Box 11)
  - General Discussion of Alternatives and Needs
  - Eagleton Amendment Regarding Flood Insurance
  - Brooke Home Assistance Section 948
  - Emergency Middle Income Housing Act
  - Foreclosure Housing Legislation, H.R. 34 and H.R. 5398 (Ashley Bill)
- Emergency Municipal Debt Guarantee Board
- Emergency Preparedness
- Empire Project - Wilkes-Barre, Pennsylvania
- Employee Suggestions
- Employment
- Energy Conservation Steering Group
- Energy Research and Development Administration
- Energy Resources Council
  - Meeting of, March 6, 1975
  - Meeting of, March 31, 1975
  - Meeting of, April 14, 1975
  - General Correspondence
  - Task Force on Thermal Standards
  - Task force on Conservation
- Environmental Impact Statement on Proposed Energy Independence Act of, 1975
- Environmental Protection Agency
- Environmental Protection Tax Act of, 1973
- Equal Housing Opportunity Hearings, Subcommittee on Civil/Constitutional Rights, House Committee on Judiciary, 9/30/76
- Equal Opportunity (Blair) (3)
- Equal Opportunity Complaint Correspondence
- Equal Opportunity Civil Rights Division Suit
- Equal Opportunity Enforcement Activities under Title 8 of the Civil Rights Act of Civil/Constitutional Rights Subcommittee, 1968
- Section 805 Enforcement of Title VIII of the Civil Rights Act of, 1968
- Estrada vs. Hills, Scope of Official Immunity
- Ethnic Purity
- Executive Identification for Development Programs
- Executive Secretariat Volume 4, January 1977
- Executive Selection/Development (Box 12)
- Expected to Reside
- Experimental Housing Allowance Program (EHAP)
- Field
  - Region I (Boston)
  - Region II (New York)
  - Region III (Philadelphia)
  - Region IV (Atlanta)
  - Region V (Chicago)
    Detroit Properties
  - Region VI (Dallas)
  - Region VII (Kansas City)
  - Region VIII (Denver)
  - Region IX (San Francisco)
  - Region X (Seattle)
- REGIONAL OPERATING PLANS (Box 12-A)
  - National Summary
  - Region I (Boston)
  - Region II (New York)
  - Region III (Philadelphia)
  - Region IV (Atlanta)
  - Region V (Chicago)
  - Region VI (Dallas)
  - Region VII (Kansas City)
  - Region VIII (Denver)
  - Region IX (San Francisco)
  - Region X (Seattle)
- Chicago FHA Scandal (Box 13)
  - Background Materials
  - Correspondence
  - Press Clips
- Field Economist Committee Report
- Chicago Regional Meeting Comments -, March 7-8, 1976
- Advance Mortgage Corporation
- Scranton Recovery Office
- Camden Area Office
- Smith, Elmer -- Equal Opportunity Investigation
- Turner, Elmo, Area Director
- Field Offices Processing Times
- Field Offices - Survey re Condition of Single and Multifamily Markets
- Field Process Evaluation System (On-Site Evaluation Reports)
- Field Operations Advisory Committee
- Field Operations Federal Executive Boards (FEBs)
- Field Operations Federal Regional Council
- Field Operations Mandatory Positions
- Field Operations Monthly Reports
- Field Operations Region Problem Issues
- Field General
- Field Operations Responses to 3/24/75 Letter
- Regional Administrators Meeting, March 24-25, 1975
- Field Operations, Meeting w/Key Field Office Staff, 3/18/75
- Field Operations, Meeting w/Key Field Office Staff, 3/20/75
- Organizational Policies, Standards and Procedures Handbook 1105.1
- Regional Operating Plans
- Secretarial Objectives re Field
- Departmental Organization
- Task Force on Separation of Contracting/Program Functions of Propert: [UNK]
- Fair Plans (Box 14)
- Fair Share Plan
- Farm Veto
- Farmers Home Administration Joint Oversight Hearing, 2/4/76
- Federal Disaster Assistance Administration (FDAA) Dunne
- FDAA-HM Relationship
- Evaluation of FHA
- FHA Interest Rate
- FHA Organization and Processing
- Federal City Council
- Federal Coordinating Council for Science, Engineering/Technology
- Federal Design Improvement Program
- Puerto Rico Disaster
- Federal Equal Housing Opportunity Council
- Federal Executive Development Program Number Two
- Federal Financing Bank Advisory Council
- Federal Home Loan Bank Board
- Federal Insurance Administration (FIA) (Hunter)
- INsurance Coordination
- Federal Insurance Administration Flood Hazard Boundary Maps
- Federal INteragency Committee on Education, Subcommittee on Education Consumer Protection.
- Federal MOrtgage Credit Programs
- Federal National Mortgage Association (FNMA)
  - FNMA General
  - FNMA Board of Directors
  - FNMA Contract
  - FNMA Task Force re HUD's Role in Regulation of FNMA
- FNMA-HUD Joint Meetings
- Federal Planning Assistance
- Federal REports Act
- Federal Reserve Banks of Philadelphia
- Federal REserve System, Board of Governors
- Federal Riot Reinsurance and Crime Insurance Program
- GOALS MANAGEMENT SYSTEM (Box 14A)
  - Status Report ending, 1/31/76
  - Status Report ending, 12/31/75
  - Status Report ending, 9/30/75
  - Status Report ending, 4/30/75
  - Status Report ending, 2/28/75
- GOALS MANAGEMENT SYSTEM -- MAJOR SECRETARIAL OBJECTIVES
  - Status Report ending, 10/31/76
  - Status Report ending, 9/30/76
  - Status Report ending, 8/31/76
  - Status Report ending, 7/31/76
  - Status Report ending, 6/30/76
  - Status Report ending, 5/31/76
  - Period Ending, April 30, 1976
  - Period Ending, March 31, 1976
  - Status Report ending, 2/29/76
  - Status Report ending, 5/31/76
  - Status Report ending, 12/31/75
- Federally Employed Women (Box 15)
- Fee Appraisal Model
- Files - HUD
- Financial Institutions Act
  - Background Materials
  - Correspondence
- Financial REport (HPMC)
- Fine Study
- Fiscal Impacts of Land Development -- A Critique of Methods and Review of Issues - HUD Research Project Report
- Flood Insurance STudies
- Flood Insurers
- Folsom Gardens Action Committee, Section 236 Operating Subsidy Case
- Foreclosure Trends
- Frank, Anthony M. - Chairman, Chief Executive Officer, Citizens Savings and Loan Association
- Freedom of Information Act
- Freedom of Information Act First Annual Report
- Freedom of Information Act (Request of Morris S. Dickey)
- Funding of FY-75 Research Projects
- Future Role of FHA
- GAO Miscellaneous
- GAO Lawsuit for the Release of IMpounded Section 235 Funds
  - Correspondence
  - Pleadings
  - Drafts
  - Section 235 Correction of Defects
  - Section 235 Home Ownership Program for Lower Income Families
- Gautreaux, Dorothy, U. S. Supreme Court, October Term, 1974
  - On Remand
- General Counsel Memoranda (Box 16)
- General Counsel Task Force re Field Counsels
- General Insurance Fund and Special Risk Insurance Fund
- Mortgage Insurance Program Section 221 (d) (2)
- Gertmenian, L. Wayne (International Liasion)
- Gift
- Glikbarg, William K.
- Goals Objectivies and Tasks for FY 76
- Government National Mortgage Association (GNMA) (Kearney)
- GNMA Mortgage Disposition Board
- GNMA Program 23
- Government Economy/Spending Reform Act of 1976 (S.2925)
  - Hearings beofre Senate Operations Committee, Subcommittee on Intergovernmental Relations
- Government Operations, Manpower and Housing Subcommittee Hearings, 7/21/75
- Government Operations, GAO Report to Chairman Manpower and Housing Subcommittee
- Greater Hartford Realtor's Plan
- Green Bay Visit
- Great Western Financial Corporation
- Growth Report, 1976
- GSA Miscellaneous
- Hampton, Project - South Central Los Angeles (Box 17)
- Handbook for Creating an Urban Development Information System
- Harris, Louis - A Study of Public Attitudes Toward Federal Government
- Hartford Case
- Harris, Patricia Roberts
- Harvard
- Harvard/MIT Joint Center for Urbanstudies -- Policy Advisory Board of Contributors Meeting
- Helsinki Agreement
- Hempstead
- Henderson Hearings
- History of HUD
- Hirsch, Werner Z., Professor of Economics
- Holly Park/Greenwood Gradens
- Home Mortgage Disclosure Act of, 1975
- Homeownership Opportunities
- Home/Property Improvement Loans
- Home Property Inventory Disposition
- House Republican STudy Group (Conservative)
  - White House - 4:00 p.m., October 8, 1975
- HAP/Section 8 Task Force
- Housing (General)
- Housing Assistance Council
- Housing Subcommittee on Manpower and Housing
- Housing Management Hearings
- Housing Management Issuances, STatus of
- Housing Management - Negotiated Sales Demonstration
- Housing Needs
- HPMC Performance Indicators
- Housing Organization, Splitting Single-Family/Multifamily Activities
- HPMC-HM Consolidation (Box 18)
- HPMC-HM Requests for Consolidation